Live your life before it passes you by
Carrie Pilby is a comedy, drama film directed by Susan Johnson.
Awkward, isolated and disapproving of most of the people around her, a precocious 19-year-old genius is
challenged to put her convictions to the test by venturing out on to the NYC dating scene.
Carrie Pilby, played by Bel Powley.
Tara, played by Vanessa Bayer.
Professor Harrison, played by Colin O'Donoghue.
Cy, played by William Moseley.
Matt, played by Jason Ritter.
Mr. Pilby, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Carrie Pilby is a 2016 American comedy-drama film directed by Susan Johnson and written by Kara
Holden and Dean Craig, based on the best-selling novel of the same name by Caren Lissner.
The film stars Bel Powley, Nathan Lane, Gabriel Byrne, Jason Ritter,
William Moseley, Vanessa Bayer, and Colin O'Donoghue.
Principal photography began on December 14, 2015, in New York City.
It was screened in the Special Presentations section at the
2016 Toronto International Film Festival.
The film was given a limited release on March 31, 2017, before being
released through video on demand on April 4, 2017, by The Orchard.
It debuted on Netflix on September 5, 2017.
The film explores themes of new york city, genius, dating, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.